{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819744645","data":{"timestamp":" 946819744645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819744868","data":{"timestamp":" 946819744868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819745831","data":{"timestamp":" 946819745831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819747105","data":{"timestamp":" 946819747105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819749947","data":{"timestamp":" 946819749947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819750790","data":{"timestamp":" 946819750790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819751102","data":{"timestamp":" 946819751102"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819752334","data":{"timestamp":" 946819752334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819755828","data":{"timestamp":" 946819755828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819756811","data":{"timestamp":" 946819756811"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819757064","data":{"timestamp":" 946819757064"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819758007","data":{"timestamp":" 946819758007"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819760844","data":{"timestamp":" 946819760844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819761876","data":{"timestamp":" 946819761876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819762348","data":{"timestamp":" 946819762348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819766869","data":{"timestamp":" 946819766868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819766924","data":{"timestamp":" 946819766924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 5759d3d0-3407-4ac4-bf01-0cf45561a646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819811758","data":{"timestamp":" 946819811758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819814180","data":{"timestamp":" 946819814180"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819857635","data":{"timestamp":" 946819857634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819859819","data":{"timestamp":" 946819859819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819892391","data":{"timestamp":" 946819892390"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819894813","data":{"timestamp":" 946819894813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819897177","data":{"timestamp":" 946819897177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819899540","data":{"timestamp":" 946819899540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819928031","data":{"timestamp":" 946819928030"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819928139","data":{"timestamp":" 946819928139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 0e03cd6d-f165-47e5-9dc1-0fe788e5f969"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819939513","data":{"timestamp":" 946819939513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819942919","data":{"timestamp":" 946819942919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819944498","data":{"timestamp":" 946819944498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819947469","data":{"timestamp":" 946819947469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819949043","data":{"timestamp":" 946819949043"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819951107","data":{"timestamp":" 946819951106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819952679","data":{"timestamp":" 946819952679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819954551","data":{"timestamp":" 946819954551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819956130","data":{"timestamp":" 946819956130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819959832","data":{"timestamp":" 946819959832"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819961401","data":{"timestamp":" 946819961401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819966006","data":{"timestamp":" 946819966004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819967574","data":{"timestamp":" 946819967574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819971005","data":{"timestamp":" 946819971004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819972572","data":{"timestamp":" 946819972572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819975450","data":{"timestamp":" 946819975450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819977016","data":{"timestamp":" 946819977016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819981021","data":{"timestamp":" 946819981020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819982619","data":{"timestamp":" 946819982619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819985462","data":{"timestamp":" 946819985462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819987064","data":{"timestamp":" 946819987064"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819990478","data":{"timestamp":" 946819990478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819992066","data":{"timestamp":" 946819992065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819994725","data":{"timestamp":" 946819994725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819996288","data":{"timestamp":" 946819996288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946819999439","data":{"timestamp":" 946819999439"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820001093","data":{"timestamp":" 946820001093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820001100","data":{"timestamp":" 946820001100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820010121","data":{"timestamp":" 946820010121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820010213","data":{"timestamp":" 946820010213"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820017332","data":{"timestamp":" 946820017332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" dc858b6b-9c45-4f7b-8de6-5b4d96b94d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820026803","data":{"timestamp":" 946820026803"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820032399","data":{"timestamp":" 946820032399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820039070","data":{"timestamp":" 946820039070"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820042930","data":{"timestamp":" 946820042929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820047693","data":{"timestamp":" 946820047693"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820053180","data":{"timestamp":" 946820053180"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820059901","data":{"timestamp":" 946820059901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820063573","data":{"timestamp":" 946820063573"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820068490","data":{"timestamp":" 946820068490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820072052","data":{"timestamp":" 946820072052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820075309","data":{"timestamp":" 946820075309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820080028","data":{"timestamp":" 946820080028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820083880","data":{"timestamp":" 946820083880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820087928","data":{"timestamp":" 946820087928"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820093346","data":{"timestamp":" 946820093346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820097921","data":{"timestamp":" 946820097921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820101790","data":{"timestamp":" 946820101790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820105846","data":{"timestamp":" 946820105846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820111829","data":{"timestamp":" 946820111829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820116141","data":{"timestamp":" 946820116141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820119976","data":{"timestamp":" 946820119976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820124775","data":{"timestamp":" 946820124774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820129988","data":{"timestamp":" 946820129988"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820134684","data":{"timestamp":" 946820134684"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820139746","data":{"timestamp":" 946820139746"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820145950","data":{"timestamp":" 946820145950"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820151303","data":{"timestamp":" 946820151302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820157089","data":{"timestamp":" 946820157087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 08e61532-53ec-432c-b167-e91fe6fb769e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820200654","data":{"timestamp":" 946820200654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820241580","data":{"timestamp":" 946820241580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820245459","data":{"timestamp":" 946820245459"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820248292","data":{"timestamp":" 946820248292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820250547","data":{"timestamp":" 946820250547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820287067","data":{"timestamp":" 946820287067"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820322804","data":{"timestamp":" 946820322804"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820322857","data":{"timestamp":" 946820322857"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" edb87989-e414-41e0-9f91-9eb32b5aee99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820331300","data":{"timestamp":" 946820331300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820335475","data":{"timestamp":" 946820335475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820339771","data":{"timestamp":" 946820339770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820343939","data":{"timestamp":" 946820343939"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820348550","data":{"timestamp":" 946820348550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820353510","data":{"timestamp":" 946820353510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820359059","data":{"timestamp":" 946820359059"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820363611","data":{"timestamp":" 946820363611"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820367890","data":{"timestamp":" 946820367890"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820373184","data":{"timestamp":" 946820373184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820378264","data":{"timestamp":" 946820378264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820382885","data":{"timestamp":" 946820382885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820389448","data":{"timestamp":" 946820389448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820396021","data":{"timestamp":" 946820396021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820400087","data":{"timestamp":" 946820400087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820404717","data":{"timestamp":" 946820404717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820410198","data":{"timestamp":" 946820410198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820416369","data":{"timestamp":" 946820416369"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820421033","data":{"timestamp":" 946820421032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820425500","data":{"timestamp":" 946820425500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820430308","data":{"timestamp":" 946820430308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820435560","data":{"timestamp":" 946820435560"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820442549","data":{"timestamp":" 946820442549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820447484","data":{"timestamp":" 946820447484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820452472","data":{"timestamp":" 946820452472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820458236","data":{"timestamp":" 946820458235"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" ab1503a0-3f7f-4367-82fb-854bb510c989"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820517155","data":{"timestamp":" 946820517155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820524749","data":{"timestamp":" 946820524749"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820535753","data":{"timestamp":" 946820535753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820553130","data":{"timestamp":" 946820553130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820574431","data":{"timestamp":" 946820574431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820583164","data":{"timestamp":" 946820583162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 12e2565a-ef76-418d-9870-1ce8c6302bc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820594222","data":{"timestamp":" 946820594221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820598031","data":{"timestamp":" 946820598031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820599610","data":{"timestamp":" 946820599610"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820602876","data":{"timestamp":" 946820602875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820604435","data":{"timestamp":" 946820604435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820608154","data":{"timestamp":" 946820608154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820609711","data":{"timestamp":" 946820609711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820613468","data":{"timestamp":" 946820613468"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820615020","data":{"timestamp":" 946820615020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820618487","data":{"timestamp":" 946820618487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820620057","data":{"timestamp":" 946820620057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820624144","data":{"timestamp":" 946820624144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820625708","data":{"timestamp":" 946820625708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820628916","data":{"timestamp":" 946820628916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820630490","data":{"timestamp":" 946820630490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820634095","data":{"timestamp":" 946820634095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820635648","data":{"timestamp":" 946820635648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820639036","data":{"timestamp":" 946820639036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820640582","data":{"timestamp":" 946820640582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820643935","data":{"timestamp":" 946820643935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820645486","data":{"timestamp":" 946820645486"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820649323","data":{"timestamp":" 946820649322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820650882","data":{"timestamp":" 946820650882"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820654584","data":{"timestamp":" 946820654584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820656142","data":{"timestamp":" 946820656142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820659955","data":{"timestamp":" 946820659955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820661501","data":{"timestamp":" 946820661500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820665001","data":{"timestamp":" 946820665001"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820666557","data":{"timestamp":" 946820666557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820670557","data":{"timestamp":" 946820670557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820672106","data":{"timestamp":" 946820672106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820676161","data":{"timestamp":" 946820676160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820677724","data":{"timestamp":" 946820677724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820681378","data":{"timestamp":" 946820681378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820682931","data":{"timestamp":" 946820682931"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820686232","data":{"timestamp":" 946820686232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820687784","data":{"timestamp":" 946820687784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820691312","data":{"timestamp":" 946820691312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820692905","data":{"timestamp":" 946820692905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820696467","data":{"timestamp":" 946820696467"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KWAHERI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820698016","data":{"timestamp":" 946820698015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820701044","data":{"timestamp":" 946820701044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820702594","data":{"timestamp":" 946820702594"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820706138","data":{"timestamp":" 946820706138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITUNGUU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820707682","data":{"timestamp":" 946820707682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820711401","data":{"timestamp":" 946820711401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KATIKATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820712960","data":{"timestamp":" 946820712960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820716034","data":{"timestamp":" 946820716034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820717616","data":{"timestamp":" 946820717616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITAMBAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820721722","data":{"timestamp":" 946820721722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITAMBAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820723292","data":{"timestamp":" 946820723291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUSOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820726517","data":{"timestamp":" 946820726516"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUSOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820728076","data":{"timestamp":" 946820728076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820731024","data":{"timestamp":" 946820731024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820732566","data":{"timestamp":" 946820732566"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KILIMANJARO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820736992","data":{"timestamp":" 946820736992"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KILIMANJARO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820738544","data":{"timestamp":" 946820738544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820741942","data":{"timestamp":" 946820741942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820743498","data":{"timestamp":" 946820743497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUKU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820746741","data":{"timestamp":" 946820746740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUKU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820748298","data":{"timestamp":" 946820748298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820751568","data":{"timestamp":" 946820751568"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820753580","data":{"timestamp":" 946820753580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820753740","data":{"timestamp":" 946820753740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_162847"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}